https://adventureland.us/adventureland-privacy-policy/

Where To Eat
F.A.Q.
Birthday Parties
Group Sales
Group Rates
Group Meal Plan
Group F.A.Q.
Where To Eat
F.A.Q.
Birthday Parties
Group Sales
Group Rates
Group Meal Plan
Group F.A.Q.
We keep your information private
Adventureland Amusement Park built the Adventureland app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by Adventureland Amusement Park at no cost and is intended for use as is.This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, anddisclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information inrelation to this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except asdescribed in this Privacy Policy.The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions,which is accessible at Adventureland unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy. Information Collection and UseFor a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to Name, email, gps location when using the app, and coupons redeemed. The information that we request is will be retained by usand used as described in this privacy policy.The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the appGoogle Play ServicesLog DataWe want to inform you that whenever you use our Service, in a case of an error in the app we collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, devicename, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing our Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.CookiesCookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your device internal memory.This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collection information and to improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent toyour device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.Service ProvidersWe may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:
To facilitate our Service;
To provide the Service on our behalf;
To perform Service-related services; or
To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
We want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.
Download The Adventureland App
Download our App from Google Play and Apple Store
APPLE STORE
GOOGLE PLAY
Useful Links
Plan A Visit
Rides & Attractions
Tickets
F.A.Q.
Accessibility Statement | Privacy Policy | Park Policies & Terms | Sitemap
Copyright 2020 © Adventureland Amusement Park. All rights Reserved. Powered by: Kick Solutions Inc.
